my life lesson is to not give up on your
dreams
when i was growing up there was a lot of
value on
education i decided to study education
because i want to help people learn
and further their own personal education
my father being an immigrant he did not
have
education and he would always mention to
myself
and my siblings take a look at my
working hands
if you do not want hands like this
pursue as much education
as you can myself and both my siblings
we just got thrown into a completely new
reality
and had no choice but to grow up fast no
one thinks it's going to happen to them
until it does
when looking through various
scholarships and the different criteria
i would always think at the back of my
head that there must be something out
there for students that have lost a
parent
when i found out about the manulife life
lesson scholarship
i was quite eager to apply
i was just doing some gardening and my
phone was ringing
inside i ran in and then answered it and
he said
i'm phoning from manulife i wanted to
congratulate you saying that you have
received the manual life life lesson
scholarship i was
i was in shock honestly this application
process was just a breeze
not giving up on my dreams is my life
lesson because you have to be able to
keep pushing forward
to be able to achieve what you want